A Guide to the Will M. Myers papers FA042
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Will M. Myers photographs, 1014; 0.3 Cubic Feet; 2 folders; 53 prints
  - William M. Myers, Some have captions attached or typed on back, 1 with slight fading, some curling; 34 prints (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Ceremonies, awards, speeches, conferences, agriculture, corn, group photo.
  - Farm Machinery, Captions attached to back, 5 with adhesive staining; 17 prints (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Agriculture, farming, machines.
  - William M. Myers, 2 prints (Box 4)